遗骸是六个小时之前发现的
Remains were found six hours ago.
我到这里的时候
By the time I got here,
他们已经在处理现场了
They were already processing the scene.
莉兹 我们可是大老远从休斯顿赶过来的
We're a long way from Houston, liz.
你为什么这么关注这件事
What's your interest in this?
我觉得受害者与我之前参与的案子有关
I think the victim's related to some cases I've been working.
他在德克萨斯州被杀 被埋到了这里 成了你的案子
Murdered in Texas,buried here,which makes it your play.
帕里斯警局的人有点抓狂
Parish pd's a little cranky about it.
我是联邦调查局特工萨格斯  你好吗
Special agent Suggs,FBI. How are you?
还可以
Good.
如你所见
Now here's what we're looking at.
一枪致命 彻底穿透
It's a single GSW,through and through.
从头骨大小来看 我认为是死者是男性青少年
The size of that skull,i'm thinking adolescent male,
大约12至14岁
Maybe 12 to 14 years old.
不 我们目前不知道性别
No, we don't know the gender.
实际上 我们是知道的  尸骨被发现时是被包裹在那条毯子里的
Actually, we do. The bones were found wrapped in that blanket.
看那个标签
Look at that tag.
“奎特曼少管所”
"QUITMAN YDF"
这是一所位于德州的男子少管所
It's an all-male juvie facility in texas.
发现尸体的人认为我们眼前的是
Guys who found him think we're looking at a friend of theirs
他们在1988年失踪的一位朋友
Who disappeared in 1988.
他们原先是狱友
They were all inmates together.
他们 什么他们
Guys? What-what guys?
是你的朋友吗
Friends of yours?
一言难尽
It's complicated.
好吧 我们去和他们聊聊
All right, let's go talk to 'em.
简直难以置信 兄弟
Unbelievable, man.
你有注意到你把土地记录给那个联邦调查局的老兄看的时候
You see how the FBI dude's eyes lit up when you showed him
他的眼睛简直在发光吗  就跟他赢了彩票一样
Those land records?Like he won the damn lottery.
是啊 这一定会成功的 各位
Yeah. No, this could work, guys.
联邦调查局的人才不会在乎雷·卡罗尔是谁
Feds don't care who Ray Carroll is,
而那些土地记录也很难轻易解释过去
And those land records are gonna be hard to explain away.
另外 我们还有莉兹在我们这边 所以 我觉得我们终于逮到他了
Plus, we got liz on our case,so,I think we finally got him.
我应该怎么做
What should I do?
什么意思
What do you mean?
卡罗尔还是要进行宣传活动的
Carroll's still got that endorsement event
就在今晚 在农场外面
Tonight out at the ranch.
那你们可能要改地方了
Maybe y'all need to move it to some place
比如说到联邦监狱去
Like the federal penitentiary.
我是认真的  我本该在一个小时内
I'm serious. I'm supposed to meet Cece
在他们家和茜茜碰面的
At the house in,like, an hour.
- 所以 我觉得我该走了  - 不 她是对的
- So,I feel like I should go.  - No, she's right.
谁知道这些警察要多久
Who knows how long it's gonna take
才能到那里呢 你们明白吧
For the cops to get there, you know?
如果她不现身 典狱长可能就会起疑
She doesn't show up,the warden might get suspicious.
那万一警察到了 而她在场呢
Well, what if they show up,and she's there?
那她就录个像呗
She'll take a damn video!
想想他在车轨上吃着野餐
Think Carroll's having a picnic on the train tracks, man.
就是这样  这次 典狱长就要倒台啦
Mm-hmm.That's it. This time,the warden's going down.
耶
yeah!
太好了
Come on!
典狱长就要倒台啦
Warden's going down!
嘿
Hey.
你去哪里了
Where have you been?
探寻人生
Figuring out my life.
呃 我待会儿再打给你
Uh, i'm gonna have to call you back.
我不能再这样下去了
I can't do this anymore.
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你 胜过我人生中的一切
I love you more than anything else in my entire life,
我 我不能让我们之间就这样结束
And I'm-I'm not gonna let this happen to us.
宝贝 我
Baby, I...
对不起
I am so sorry.
我从来没有想伤害过你 我
I never meant to hurt you. I...
你怎么了
What happened to you?
事情都结束了
It's over.
警方正在审问典狱长
The police are questioning the warden,
我认为 他会因为涉嫌谋杀
And I think he's gonna go down for the murder
一个我们在奎特曼时期失踪的孩子而入狱
Of a kid who disappeared while we were at Quitman.
我想你回来 宝贝
I want you back, baby.
我想你回家
I want you to come home.
请告诉我你愿意让我回到你身边
Tell me you'll take me back, please.
我好想你
I have missed you so much.
我 我爱你
I... I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你想再听点疯狂的事吗
You want to hear something crazy?
什么
What?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
我们要
We're gonna...?
我们要有孩子了
We're gonna have a baby?
虽然我很确定是我一个人
I'm pretty sure i'm gonna be doing
来做生孩子的大部分事情 但是 确实是的
Most of the work, but, yeah.
你敢相信吗
Can you believe that?
好了 州长会在6:00到达
All right,the governor arrives at 6:00.
在此之前 我们要先在门廊上招待来宾
We'll do the meet-and-greet before, ops on the porch.
杰西在哪里
Where is jessie?
迟到可不像她的作风
This is so unlike her to be late.
6:30 和房间内的人周旋
At 6:30, working the room,
活动7:00准时开始 可以吗
Then the program will start at 7:00 sharp, all right?
雷
Ray?
好的
Yeah.
计划不错
Uh, that's good.
等我一会儿
Just give me a minute.
雷·卡罗尔
Ray carroll?
- 是我  - 我是联邦调查局特工萨格斯
- Yes.  - Special agent Suggs. FBI.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
上一次你看到这个男孩还活着是什么时候
When's the last time you saw this boy alive?
就像我之前说过的一样
Like I told you before,
就在事故之后
It was right after the accident.
他们把他带到了医务室
They brought him in to the infirmary.
我让一个警卫把他带上了一辆面包车
I had one of the guards put him in a van,
送他去了急诊室
Take him to the emergency room.
你知道面包车离开之后发生了什么吗
Know what happened after the van left?
我一直以为他们把他带到了医院
Well,I always assumed they took him to the hospital.
但是他从来没有回来过
But when he never came back,
我问过早班护士这件事
I asked the day nurse about it, and
她说他们出于医疗条件原因
She said they transferred him to another facility
把他送到了另一个设施机构
For medical reasons.
你有签署相关文件吗
Did you sign off on the paperwork?
噢 当然有
Oh, I'm sure I did.
我们在那次骚乱中丢失了所有的文件记录
We lost all those records in the riot,
但是当时记录都是按标准程序走的
But that would have been standard procedure.
你还记得你在1988年8月
Do you recall purchasing
购置的路易斯安那州边界上的那块地吗
Land on the Louisiana border in August of 1988?
对 我记得
Yeah,I remember this.
那块地打鸟应该很好
Supposed to be good bird hunting.
它怎么了
What about it?
今早我们就是这块你在这个男孩失踪三天后
Well, that's where we found the remains this morning,
购置的土地区域内在发现的尸体残骸
On land that you purchased three days after this boy disappeared.
你有什么要解释的吗
You have any explanations for that?
呃
Hmm.
这
Well...
一定是雷德和博比
Red and Bobby.
什么
Excuse me?
我在奎特曼的时候有两个为我工作的警卫
There were two guards that worked for me at Quitman.
我带他们去那里打过几次猎
I took them there hunting a couple times.
他们知道这片地在哪里
They knew where this land was.
一定是他们把他埋到了那里
They must have buried him there.
他们为什么会想杀掉这个男孩
Why would they want to kill this boy?
我不知道
I don't know.
那时候他们就一直给我惹麻烦
They were always a problem--
和犯人打架 给犯人卖毒品偷偷赚外快
Fighting with the inmates,running deals on the side.
事故发生的时候
They were in charge of the work detail
是他们负责具体工作的
When the accident happened.
可能他们只是受到了惊吓 比较紧张
Maybe they just got scared and panicked,
而杀掉那个男孩就是他们的解决办法
This was their solution.
你知道博比·马克斯已经死了
You are aware that Bobby Marks is deceased,
而雷德·泰森15年前就已经失踪了吗
Red Tyson disappeared 15 years ago?
我知道
I'm aware.
那你这就太方便了吧
That seems very convenient.
你把一切罪责都推给两个无法给自己申辩的人
You blaming two men who can't tell their side of the story.
萨格斯先生 我不喜欢你话中的暗喻
Mr.Suggs,I don't like what you're implying,
所以我和你说清楚
So let me be clear.
我与此无关 你也无法证明我身涉其中
I'm not involved in this,and you can't prove that I am.
我已经很耐心了 请你也适可而止
Now I've been very patient,and enough is enough.
现在我要去忙我一天的工作了
Now I need to get about my day,
请你们俩滚出我的房子
And you two need to get the hell off of my property
不要再诬陷我一些我根本没做过的事
And quit accusing me of something i didn't do.
嗨
Hi.
哦 终于来了
Uh, there she is.
各位 请给我们一点时间
Guys, give us some time.
刚刚那是怎么回事
What was that all about?
他们是来调查什么来自布朗斯维尔的人
Well, they're investigating some guy from brownsville
地皮契约的事情 警方想要背景信息
For rigging state contracts,and they wanted background.
就好像我有时间管这破事一样
Like I have time for that now.
为什么联调局会来
Why is the FBI involved?
因为他们想呗 茜茜
'cause they just are, cece.
不是你需要担心的问题
Not for you to worry about,
所以别管了
So drop it.
你好啊 杰西
How are you doing, jessie?
嗨
Hi.
雷 你要去哪
Oh, where-where you going, ray?
我要自己开车去农场
Ah. I'm gonna drive myself out to the ranch,
用开车的时间来练习一下我的演讲
Use the windshield time to work on my speech.
待会见
I'll see you there later.
我以为是你要开车送他去
I thought you were driving him.
我也这样以为
I thought I was, too.
哦 我的天呐
Oh, my god. Um...
怎么了
What's wrong?
我妈妈刚刚发短信给我
My mom just texted me.
说家里的水管爆裂了 水流得到处都是
A pipe broke, and there is water everywhere.
我恐怕得回家处理这件事了
I'm gonna have to go home and deal with this.
你需要我找人开车送你回去吗
You want me to have someone drive you?
没事  我自己可以的
No. I got it.
我只是要先处理这件事
I will just go take care of this,
然后我会直接去农场的了
And then, I will head to the ranch straight after.
我们需要你在那里 杰西
We need you there, jessie.
我得去处理这件事 好吗
I'm just gonna go deal with this, okay?
他在说谎 莉兹  你知道的
Oh, he is lying, liz.You know that.
所以 所以 你想要我们怎么办
So-so what do...What do you want us to do?
我知道了  好的
I know. Yeah.
好的 再见
Yeah. Bye.
他把这件事推到了雷德和博比身上
He blamed it on red and bobby.
所以呢  他们不打算逮捕他了吗
So, what? They're not gonna arrest him now?
他们不能逮捕他
Well, they can't.
这是他一人之言
It's his word against
责怪雷德 博比 和艾米
Red, bobby and amy.
而他们都死了 所以警方没办法
They're all dead, so they got
继续调查下去
Nothing to go on.
那那些在属于他的地里挖出来的人骨怎么解释
What about the human bones all over his property?
你想要我说什么 吉尔
What do you want me to say, Gil?
我们都知道是他做的  但是我们没办法证明这件事
We know he did it.We just can't prove it.
也许他没有做呢
Maybe he didn't.
不可能 肖恩
No way, shawn.
在联调局的人离开后我看到了他的表情
I saw him after the fbi left.
他完全被吓到了
He was completely spooked.
想想吧
Think about it.
典狱长完全就是在用手段来操控别人
The warden's whole play is to leverage people.
对吧  让别人替他干脏活
Right? Make someone else do his dirty work for him.
在奎特曼的时候谁是他最忠诚的走狗啊
Who were the biggest lap dogs the entire time at quitman?
特里和他手下
Terry and his crew.
如果他逼他们做那些事呢
What if he made them do it?
E区
E block.
对  我是说 这些人
Right. I mean those guys had
拍马屁都拍得快把头凑到马屁股上了
Their heads so far up the warden's ass,
他们从不用劳动 所以
They never had to do work detail, so,
- 也许他们是 - 他们也在同一个牢房
- Maybe if they were the ones that... - They were in the same
那就意味着雷德得去E区接他们
Bunkroom, that means red went to e block to get 'em.
他把他们带去找典狱长  那说得通
He took 'em to the warden.That makes sense.
所以你想做什么
So what do you want to do?
直接去问特里 问他
Walk up to terry, ask him
- 是不是杀了人 - 不是
- If they did it? - No.
我们去和他弟弟谈一谈
We go and talk to his brother.
联调局的人来我家里 指控我谋杀
I had the FBI at my house,accusing me of murder.
冷静点
Just calm down.
我们一直都知道这是有可能发生的
We always knew this was a possible problem.
你知道谁在背后作祟 对吧
You know who's behind this,don't you?
杰克逊·布鲁克斯
Jackson brooks.
他们是这样跟你说的吗
Did they tell you that?
他们没必要和我说我也知道
They didn't have to!
我一直告诉你他是个麻烦
I've been telling you for a month he's trouble,
而你却无动于衷
And you haven't done anything.
他们有房契证明 戴安娜
They have the deed records, diana.
你觉得他们花多长时间才会发现
How long you think it's gonna take
我把那块地卖了给你
For them to figure out i sold that land to you?
没关系的
It doesn't matter.
这种事有偶然性能解释
There's a contingency in place for that.
你没必要担心这种事  坐下吧
You don't need to worry about it. Have a seat.
我现在不想坐下
I don't want to sit down.
雷蒙德
Raymond!
在这件事上我已经花了太多心血投资太多钱财
I've worked too long, and i've invested too much in this
你现在可不能给我毁了
For you to blow it for me now.
你不开心了 我能理解
You're upset, and i understand,
但是不开心的人容易犯错 而我不喜欢错误
But upset people make mistakes,and i don't like mistakes.
- 要是媒体收到风声的话  - 媒体不会知道的 我保证
- If the press gets wind of this, i...- They won't.Just trust me.
所以 以下是我想要你做的事
So here's what i want you to do.
我想要你深呼吸
I want you to take a deep breath.
然后振作起来
I want you to pull yourself together,
然后你去你的派对
And i want you to go to your party.
你会和几个人握握手
You're gonna shake a few hands,
然后你会做个不错的演讲
You're gonna make a nice speech,
六个月之后
And then in six months,
我们会在国会大厦那里给你一间办公室
We will open your office on capitol hill.
我不是一个信教的人
I ain't no religious man.
我在我人生中犯过很多错误
Made a lot of mistakes in my life.
当你来找我寻求原谅的时候
When you came to me asking about forgiveness,
我直接告诉了你  我做不到
I told you straight-- i can't do that
我不能原谅你对我做的事
For what you did to me.
但这是不同的 丹尼斯
But this is different, dennis.
我们在说的可是
We're talking about
一个12岁的男孩在头上被开了一枪
A 12-year-old boy shot through the head
然后像垃圾一样被埋在野外
And buried in a field like a piece of trash.
我知道你知道那是不对的
I know you know that's not right.
而我也知道这让你很困扰
And i know it bothers you.
所以如果你真的是你说的那个人
So if you're really who you say you are,
那么现在是时候去证明了
Now's the time to prove it.
我不知道你想从我这里得到什么
I don't know what you want from me.
我们想要真相 丹尼斯
We want the truth, dennis.
而且我们认为是典狱长杀了他 我们
And we think the warden did this, and we think
认为你知道发生了什么
You know what happened.
博比和艾米护士告诉我们雷德那天去
Bobby and nurse amy told us red came to e block
E区接走了你们
And got you guys that day.
你和他们说过话
You talked to them?
那是真的吗  雷德真的来了然后接走了你们俩带你们去见典狱长了吗
Is it true? Did red come and get you and take you to the warden?
达瑞尔和埃迪没有和我们一起去
Darryl and eddie weren't with us.
就只有我和特里
It was just me and terry.
所以你也在现场吗
So you were there?
发生了什么
What happened?
雷德进来  他看起来非常严肃的样子
Red came in. He was looking really serious.
他来接走我们 他带我们上了他的车
Uh, and he came and got us,and he put us in his car.
然后就是 你知道的 我在小货车里
Next thing you know,i'm riding in some van.
跟典狱长和皮蒂一起吗
With the warden and petey?
对的
Yeah.
在我上车的时候我并不知道
I didn't know if petey was alive or dead
皮蒂是死了还是活着
By the time i got into the van.
我们开了二十多分钟去路易斯安那
We drove about 20 minutes into louisiana.
然后到了一处不知道是哪的荒郊野外
Ended up in a field somewhere in the middle of nowhere.
然后
Then...
那就是这件事发生的时候了
That's when it happened.
我一直都对你们俩兄弟很好 对吧
I've always taken real good care of you boys, haven't i?
给你们特权
Given you special privileges,
让你们做别的犯人不能做的事 对吧
Let you do things other inmates can't?
那是因为那些权利是你们争取得来的
That's because you've earned it.
你们很聪明
You're smart.
你们知道我做事的方式 而我很欣赏这一点
You know how i do things,and i respect that.
我们三个有很特殊的关系
The three of us have a very special relationship,
而我想继续这种特殊关系
And i'd like to keep that going.
你们想不想继续呢
Wouldn't you?
想  先生
Yes, sir.
我们现在有一件很不幸运的事情要发生
We have an unfortunate situation here.
这个男孩是熬不过去了
This boy is not gonna make it.
而人道的做法是
and the humane thing to do
让他从痛苦中解脱
Is to put him out of his misery.
所以你们之中的哪一个想表达你的感激之情
So which one of you is gonna show me his appreciation?
你们中的哪一个会有这样的男子气概
Which one of you is gonna be a man
去做该完成的事
And step up and do what needs to be done?
让我看看
Show me.
我知道我本可以更坚强一些的
I know i could have been stronger.
这不是你的错
It wasn't your fault.
典狱长才是主谋  特里往皮蒂的头上
It was the warden that did this.Terry put a bullet
开了一枪
In petey's head.
杀人不眨眼
Cold blood, point blank.
甚至不觉得自己有罪过
And he didn't even feel bad about it.
我的兄弟是个杀手
My brother is a killer.
以前是 一直都是
He always has been, he always will be.
你需要告诉检察官这些
You need to go to the d.A.
不
No.
你是帮凶  丹尼斯
You're an accessory to murder, Dennis.
典狱长会因此下台
The warden is gonna go down for this,
不用想也知道他会拉你下水
And don't think for a second he is not gonna take you with him.
杰克森说得对 除非
Jackson's right. Unless
你把真相讲出来 得到豁免权
You tell the truth and you get immunity,
不然你的余生都会待在监狱里的
You're going to jail for the rest of your life.
所有这些 你所有的努力都会付诸东流
All of this, everything you've worked for is gone.
你知道你在让我做什么吗
Do you understand what you're asking me to do?
你让我背叛我的亲兄弟
You want me to betray my own brother?!
听我说
Listen to me!
你们流着同样的血 但他不是你的兄弟
Y'all have the same blood, but he is not your brother.
你不像他 你比他要好
You ain't like him. You're better than he is.
这是唯一的方法了
This is the only way.
现在就看你了
This is your time
不要动摇
To be stronger.
悬崖勒马吧
Save yourself while you still can.
发生了什么
What's going on?
我们搞定他了 宝贝
We got him, baby.
典狱长吗
The Warden?
是的  还有特里 他的兄弟说典狱长
Yeah. Terry, too. His brother said the Warden
带他们去了那个地方 让特里杀了皮蒂
Took them out to that field, made Terry kill Petey.
他正在这里 告诉检察官一些事
He's in there telling the d.A. Right now.
为什么弄这么久
I don't know why it's taking so long.
他们在这里已经有一个小时了
They've been in there for an hour.
他们来了
Hey, they're coming.
丹尼斯 进展怎么样
Hey, Dennis, how'd it go?
丹尼斯
Dennis.
怎么了
What happened?
他给了我们一份签署声明 我的助理
He gave us a signed statement. My assistant's
正在整理特里·鲍施涉嫌谋杀的逮捕令
Putting together a murder warrant on Terry Bausch.
很好 那么关于那个
All right, that's good. What about
- 典狱长呢 - 谁
- The warden?  - Who?
雷·卡罗尔 谁在安排他的逮捕令
Ray Carroll. Who's putting the warrant together on him?
没有提过他
Didn't say anything about him.
丹尼斯
Dennis.
为什么你不告诉他们典狱长的事
Why didn't you tell 'em about the warden?
不管你是谁 不要和他说话
Whoever this is, don't talk to him.
这是谁 你有律师了吗 先生
What... Who the hell is this? You got an attorney now? Sir.
为什么你要说谎  为什么你要说谎
Why'd you lie? Why'd you lie?
谁找上你了 丹尼斯 丹尼斯
Who got to you, dennis！ Dennis!
有些事不对劲 我们漏了什么
Something's wrong. What are we missing?
丹尼斯怂了 仅此而已
Dennis got scared, that's all.
想到他因为出卖自己的兄弟就已经有足够多的麻烦了
Figured he's in enough trouble selling out his brother,
也不想典狱长找到他
Doesn't want the warden to come after him, too.
你不能像这样糊弄检察官
You can't screw with the d.A. Like that.
只要发现他在说谎 他的豁免权就没有了
As soon as they figure out he's lied, his immunity's gone.
他这是在自掘坟墓
He's digging his own grave.
就像在路易斯安那州挖的那个
Just like the one he dug in Louisiana.
什么意思
What was that?
啊
Huh?
你刚才说什么
What did you say?
就像 在路易斯安那州挖的那个
Just... Like the one he dug in Louisiana.
路易斯安那州
Louisiana.
就是它 就是它
Oh, that's it, that's it.
杰克逊
Jackson!
嘿 你要去哪里
Hey, where you going?
我们去找检察官
We're going back to the d.A.
我有一个办法
I have an idea.
是中性的 因为你不知道
It's gender-neutral, since you don't know
你怀的是男孩还是女孩
If you're having a boy or a girl,
- 对吧 - 还不知道
- So... Right? - Not yet.
谢谢你 戴安娜 你不必专程
Thank you, diana.You didn't have to
过来一趟给我这个
Come all the way here to give me this.
没事 我想看看你
It's okay, i-i wanted to check on you
看你怎么样了
And just see how you were doing.
实际上好多了
Much better, actually.
杰克逊和我已经和好了
Jackson and I have patched things up.
噢 真好
Oh, that's wonderful.
为你感到非常开心
I'm very happy for you.
戴安娜 为什么你要雇佣我们公司
Diana, why did you hire our firm?
因为你
Because of you.
但是你认识艾伦很长时间了 是吗
But you've known Aaron a long time, right?
是的 当他告诉我 他的合伙人
Yes, and when he told me that his partner
是个了不起的律师
Was a terrific lawyer,
艾伦觉得我会喜欢和听取她的意见
Whom he thought that i would like, i listened.
怎么
Why?
我很担心你和雷·卡罗尔的关系
I'm concerned about your relationship with Ray Carroll.
他怎么了
What about him?
杰克逊告诉了我一些事
Jackson has told me some things.
他贪赃枉法
That he's corrupt.
是吗
Well...
我就不知道了
I-i wouldn't know about that.
我听说雷·卡罗尔会因为谋杀被逮捕入狱
I heard ray carroll is gonna be arrested for murder.
真的吗
Really?
涉嫌一个犯人
It involves an inmate
在他还是奎特曼少管所典狱长的任职期间消失了
Who disappeared while he was warden at quitman.
你是今早在新闻上看到的么
Did you hear this on the news this morning?
没有 还没说
No. It hasn't happened just yet.
你一点都不知情吗
You didn't know about any of this?
完全不知道
Absolutely not.
难以相信
I'm shocked.
正如我一直常说的
This is just exactly what i'm talking about.
我真幸运
I am lucky
有你替我注意着 所以
That i have you watching out for me, so...
我马上去拿我的政府事务文件
I'll get my government affairs on this right away.
我就不打扰你了 但是还是要
And i'll get out of your hair now, but...
谢谢你的提醒
Thanks for the heads-up.
我很高兴来了一趟
I'm really glad that i stopped by.
在这期间 雷
During these times... Ray.
我觉得杰西·韦斯特有问题
I think we have a problem with jessie west.
有一天我工作很晚
The other night i was working late
然后我听见一些噪音从你的办公室传来
And i hear a noise from your office.
我过去检查 发现没有人在那儿
So i went to check it out, nobody was there.
但是有一个抽屉是半开着的
But one of the drawers was half open
还有尤德·汉姆的捐助文件不见了
And jud hamm's donor file was missing.
所以
So?
所以我觉得是她拿走了文件 她是内奸
So i think she took it. I think she's a mole.
我想她是为反对派工作的
I think she's working for the opposition's campaign.
小杰西
Little jessie?
她就是个花瓶
She's just eye candy.
直觉告诉我 她一直表现很怪
It's a hunch. She's been acting strange.
你在胡思乱想
You're being paranoid.
那个女孩不是内奸
That girl is not a mole.
就算她是 我领先18分
And even if she is, i'm 18 points ahead--
那她的活儿干得真不怎么样
She must not be very good at it.
我就是想跟你说说
I just wanted to bring it up.
好吧
All right.
典狱长带你去了那个地方 他给你一把枪
The warden took you out to that field, he gave you a gun
然后胁迫你杀了皮蒂 是不是
And he made you kill petey, didn't he?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
听我说
All right, listen to me.
你的兄弟供出你了
Your brother gave you up.
他告诉了我们所有事 我们正要去警局
He told us everything and we're going to the police,
但是我们的目标不是你 我们要典狱长
But we don't want you, we want the warden.
那个人是个魔鬼
That man is the devil.
你知道他带你越过边境的唯一原因
You know the only reason he took you over the border
然后逼你做了那些事
And made you do it there
是因为在路易斯安那州 胁迫不能作为辩护理由
Is because duress is not a defense in louisiana,
就是说即使他拿枪抵着你的头
Which means even if he put a gun to your head...
逼你开枪
And made you shoot...
你还是会因为谋杀坐牢
You're still going down for murder.
你明白吧
You understand that?
典狱长控制了我们
The warden manipulated us,
他利用我们
He used us,
然后他会拉你陪葬除非你帮助我们
And he's gonna take you down unless you help us.
这是你唯一的出路
This is your way out.
现在我给你这个方法
I am giving it to you.
所有一切都可以现在结束
All of it can end right now.
所有仇恨
All the bad blood,
所有斗争 所有事情
All the fighting everything.
你只需要
All you have to do...
告诉人们真相
Is tell the truth.
你以为我像你想的那样愚蠢 是吗 律师
Just how stupid do you think i am, lawyer, hmm?
告诉你们真相
Tell you the truth?
转过身去  搜搜他的身
Turn around. Check him for a tail.
嗯
Huh?
好了 去把车开过来  快点
All right, go get the car. Hurry up.
快快快 动作快点
Hurry up, make it quick.
有可疑动作
Suspect on the move.
我们看到了
We got a visual!
下车
Get out of the vehicle!
停止开火  杰克逊在他手里
Hold your fire. He's got jackson.
把车门打开
Open the door.
停火
Hold your fire.
噢 啊
Oh, aah!
好的 可以  没问题
Okay, that's affirmative. On our way.
你还好吧
You okay?
嗯 没事
Yeah, i'm okay.
他逃跑了
He got away.
什么 哦不
What? No.
他逃了
He got away.
噢 拜托
Aw, man.
杰克逊还好吗
Is jackson okay?
应该没事的
Should be fine.
跟你说 这是我见过的最勇敢的事情
I tell you what-- it's the bravest thing I've ever seen.
我只是不能相信特里逃跑了
I just... I can't believe terry got away!
听着 联调局在呢 他们肯定会找到他的
Look, it's the FBI-- I'm sure they're gonna find him.
噢 那又怎么样 杰西
Oh, what's it matter, jessie?
好了 宝贝
Okay, babe...
你需要冷静点
You need to calm down.
听着 特里知道如果他被抓了
Listen, terry knows if he gets arrested,
他后半辈子都要在监狱里度过
He's going to prison for the rest of his life.
他不可能会让自己被他们
There is no chance he's gonna let them
活捉的
Take him alive.
也就是说典狱长也逍遥法外了
Which means the warden gets away, too.
也许你需要再去和丹尼斯谈谈
Maybe you go talk to Dennis again.
怎么谈  我们根本不知道他在哪儿
How? We have no idea where he is!
吉尔 我明白
Gil, i know that.
我只是想帮帮忙
I'm just trying to help.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
对不起 我
I'm sorry, it's...
噢 就差那么一点就抓到他了
Oh, we were so close.
典狱长的派对什么时候开始
What time is the warden's party?
什么
What?
竞选集会
The endorsement thing.
我们还有时候赶过去 对吧
We still have time to get there, right?
- 为什么要过去 - 因为我想到了个办法
- Why would we want to do that? - Because I have an idea.
但我自己干不了  你会帮我吗
But I can't do it by myself. Will you help me?
我过会儿就来
I'll catch up with you.
好没问题
Yeah, great.
我是温特斯
Winters.
莉兹 我是特里
Liz, it's terry.
你旁边没人吧
You alone?
没人  你想干嘛
Yeah. What do you want?
太好了  听着 我中了那个律师的埋伏
All right, good. Look, I got ambushed. Lawyer set me up.
现在联调局正在追我
FBI's after me right now.
等等 等等 什么律师 你慢点说  是杰克逊·布鲁克斯吗
Wait, wait, what, what lawyer? Slow down. Jackson Brooks?
听着 我没时间
Look, i don't have time
跟你解释了 好吗
To explain to you, all right?
我需要拿到我的应急包
Look, i need my go bag.
它在我房子后面那个棚子的墙角柜里
It's in the shed behind my house, the corner cabinet.
你去取过来带给我
You're gonna grab it and you're gonna bring it to me
只能是你自己行动
And you're gonna be alone.
我要滚回墨西哥了
I'm getting my ass to Mexico.
什么 你疯了吗 特里  我不可能
What, are you crazy, Terry? There is no way
妨碍联邦调查局的追捕行动
I'm getting involved in a federal manhunt.
不然我就杀了你弟弟
I'm gonna kill your brother.
懂了吗 探长
You understand that, detective?
这对你来说不费吹灰之力
It's as easy as a phone call away,
所以 别在那儿傻坐着
So don't you sit there and pretend
你没有选择可言
That you got a choice here.
今晚10点
Now, you're gonna meet me at 10:00 tonight,
到加尔维斯顿61号街码头来见我
61st street pier at galveston.
把我的包带上 只能你自己来
Bring the bag and come alone.
不然你再看到罗比的时候 你就去给他收尸吧
Or the next time you see Robby, he's gonna be in a bag.
我不会让你这么做
I'm not letting you do this.
你说过我们要去的 所以起来吧
You said we were going, so get up.
这有什么意义呢
What's the point?
意义在于 艾米是你的朋友
The point is, Amy was your friend.
你需要表示你的尊重
And you need to pay your respects.
你不明白吗
Don't you understand?
我们一直以来所做的一切
Everything that we've worked for--
靴弟走后我们做的一切都成为了徒劳
Everything that's happened since boots is all for nothing.
特里逃跑了
Man, terry's getting away,
典狱长自然也脱了干系
The warden's getting away,
这整件事全乱套了
The whole thing is a big damn mess,
所以对不起 我没心情去一个
So excuse me if I don't feel like going to the funeral
因我而死的女人的葬礼
For a woman I helped get killed.
肖恩 看着我
Shawn, look at me.
今天早晨我起床
I woke up this morning
梳好头发  化好妆
And i curled my hair. And i did my makeup.
然后穿上了这条裙子
And i put on this dress.
你知道我上次穿这条裙子是在什么时候吗
And do you know the last time i wore this dress?
是在我自己丈夫的葬礼上
It was to my own husband's funeral.
那你知道我为什么这么做吗
And you know why i did that?
是为了你  为了帮你
For you. To help you.
就像你以前帮我的那样帮你
The same way that you have been helping me.
不是只有你一个人会悲伤
You don't have a franchise on grief.
现在
So...
去找一件外套穿上然后上车
Go find a suit and you get your ass to my car,
我们必须去葬礼 肖恩
Because we are going to this funeral, shawn.
立刻
Right now.
准备好出发了吧
We're good to go.
是的
I think so.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你好
Hello?
嗨 纳格尔夫人 我是简妮
Hi, ms. Nagle, it's Janey
这里是帕森医生的办公室  你还好吗
Calling from dr. Parson's office. How are you?
嗨 简妮 我很好 谢谢你
Hi, janey. I'm good, thank you.
我们拿到你12周的产检结果了
So, we got the labs back from your 12-week visit,
所有指标都很正常
And everything looks great.
太好了
Good.
你想知道你怀的是男孩还是女孩吗
Do you want to know what you're having?
噢 帕森医生看了超声波
Uh, dr. P looked at the ultrasound,
所以我可以告诉你是男还是女
So i can tell you if it's a boy or a girl.
如果你想知道的话
If you want to know.
哦 我想知道
Actually, i do.
是个男孩  恭喜你
Well, it's a boy. Congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
这学校不错  我女儿去年五月从这儿毕业
It's a fine school. She graduated last may
然后搬去了华盛顿  她想在国会山工作
And moved to d.C. She wants to work on the hill.
噢
Oh,
我认识一个人
I know somebody who just
他好像正在招人
Might be hiring.
是吧 雷蒙德
Right, raymond?
啊什么
Excuse me?
你可以帮忙给他们的女儿安排一个职位吧
Maybe you could give their daughter a job on your staff.
在你赢得选举之后
After you win this thing.
噢 当然没问题  让她打给我吧
Uh, yeah. Have her give me a call.
失陪一会儿
Excuse me for a moment.
雷
Ray,
州长来了 你要过去问声好
Now, the governor's arrived, so you have to greet him.
州长 很高兴见到您
Governor, good to see you.
见到您太棒了  你还记得我的助手吗
Great, it's great to see you. You remember my assistant
这位 呃
Here, uh...
- 嘿 - 天呐
- Hey. - Geez!
我们谈谈
I need to talk to you.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我想让你打给特里 让我们见一面
I want you to call terry, set up a meeting.
什么 你想让我干什么
You want me to what?
我知道他现在在逃  我知道他
I know he's on the run. I know he's...
也许不会回应
Probably won't answer,
但我猜你们俩应该还有联系 是吧
But i'm assuming you two are in contact, right?
我是不会放弃的
'cause i am not giving up on this.
我不会让他跑掉的
I'm not letting him get away,
所以我要你打给他  你想尽办法让他来见你
So i want you to call him. You tell him whatever you have to
然后你把他逮捕起来
To get him to meet you and then you're gonna arrest him.
我觉得你今天已经累了  你需要回家休息
I think you've had a long day. You need to go home.
莉兹  莉兹
Liz. Liz.
你不用再担心了
You don't have to worry anymore.
你弟弟我已经安排妥当
I took care of your brother.
我跟地方检察官说过了
I spoke to the d.A.
我告诉她 他是贪污案的检举人
I told her he's an informant in one of my rico cases.
他需要保护 他们已经把他转移走了
He needs protection, and they've already moved him.
他安全了
He is safe.
特里碰不到他了 你不用再提心吊胆了
Terry can't get to him, and you don't have to be afraid.
你还好吗
Okay. You okay?
我们联系过了
We've been in touch.
他一个小时前给我打了电话
He called me an hour ago.
他说什么
What did he say?
他说他要逃到国外去
He told me he's fleeing the country,
他让我拿上他的应急包
And... He needs me to get his go bag
然后去加尔维斯顿港的61号码头找他
And to meet him at the 61st street pier in Galveston.
- 61号  - 去他的仓库 不然罗比就得死
- 61st. - At his warehouse or else Robby's dead.
所以你不用再担心了啊  莉兹
Which you don't have to worry about anymore. Liz,
莉兹 这是好事  是好事
Liz, this is good. This is so good.
你去见他  然后逮捕他
You're gonna meet him. You're gonna arrest him,
我会解释一切  告诉他我想出了这个办法
And I will explain everything. I will say I got a tip.
我带你去找他
I led you to him.
不行  他会把我为他做的那些事
No. And then he tells the whole world what i've been doing
- 都公之于众  - 没关系的  莉兹 不过是杀人犯的胡言乱语
- for him. - It doesn't matter. Liz, Liz, that is the word
一个毒贩子抵抗警察的逮捕罢了
of a murderer and a... And a drug dealer against a cop.
不会有人相信他的
No one will believe him.
我为你担保
I will vouch for you.
不 我必须自己去  如果他看见你了 那就前功尽弃了
No, i need to go alone. If he sees you, we lose him.
- 我必须自己去  - 好吧
- I need to do this alone. - All right.
莉兹 谢谢你
Liz, thank you.
你做得到的
You got this.
愿她的灵魂能追随圣者的脚步
And grant her entrance into thy kingdom
踏入你们的宫殿
in the fellowship of saints,
愿上帝保佑 伟大的主  阿门
through jesus christ, our lord. Amen.
阿门
Amen.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你是肖恩·库克吗
Are you Shawn Cook?
是的
Yeah.
我是弗雷德 艾米的外甥
I'm fred, uh, amy's nephew.
我有东西给你
I have something for you.
今天早上 我在整理姨妈的车时
I was cleaning out my auntie's car this morning when i found
- 在座椅下面发现了这个  - 这是什么
- This under the seat. - What is it?
我不知道  但是我想应该交给你
I don't know. But i figured you should have it, so...
谢谢
Thanks.
节哀顺变
I'm sorry for your loss.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你来晚了
You were late today.
是
Yeah.
抱歉  我家的水管坏了
I'm sorry. There was a pipe that broke in our house,
- 我得帮我妈妈  - 这样啊
- So i had to help my mom.- Ah.
不过 派对还挺好的  是吧
The party's going great, though. Don't you think?
我想和你谈谈
We need to have a conversation.
好的
Okay.
私下谈
In private.
艾米说的就是这个
This is what amy was talking about.
- 这是什么  - 奎特曼的孩子们
- What is it? - Kids from quitman.
她任职时 所有去过医疗室的病人名单
Everybody who came through the infirmary while she was there,
然后他们就被送到医院去了  但是这些人
Then got sent to the hospital. But these here,
应该是回来了
Looks like they came back.
拿这些重点标出来的呢
What are the highlighted ones?
你看 亚伦·格鲁贝
All right, see, Aaron Grube,
- 嗯  - 没有记录  唐特利·拉什 没有记录
- Mm-hmm. - No record. Uh, Dontelle Rush, no record.
马里奥·丰特
Mario Fuente...
等一下
Wait a minute.
- 这个D R  - 嗯
- That "D R," right? - Mm-hmm.
指的就是唐特利·拉什  首字母一样
Same as Dontelle Rush. Same initials.
所以这说明了什么
So what does that mean?
说明我们是对的
It means we were right.
皮蒂不是唯一一个被杀掉的孩子
Petey wasn't the only one who was killed.
走吧
Come on.
塔特尔认为你是我的对手安插在
So, Tuttle thinks you're a mole working
我竞选团队里的内奸
for my opponent's campaign.
什么
What?
一派胡言
That's ridiculous.
我也是这么说的
That's what i said.
你是吗
So, are you?
不是 卡罗尔先生
Mr. Carroll, no.
我不知道这些谣言从何而来
Look, i don't know where this is coming from, but there's
但是外面一百多位重要来宾都在等你
A hundred very important people waiting for you.
我们必须出去了
We need to go outside.
你以为我不记得你 是不是
You don't think i remember you, do you?
小杰西·韦斯特
Little Jessie West.
穿着碎花裙子的金发女孩儿
Cute blonde girl in a flower print dress
布伦南一路骑着自行车
Who rode her bike all the way from Brennan
来见一些朋友
To see her friends. You looked
你那天好像吓坏了
Very scared that day.
现在也一样
Just like you do now.
你要告诉我这到底是怎么回事吗
You want to tell me what's going on?
没有任何事情
There's nothing's going on.
别弄得太难看 杰西
This doesn't have to get ugly, Jessie.
你知道我会查清楚的  所以 不如现在就告诉我
You know i'm gonna find out. So why don't you tell me
你的同伙是谁 你们来这儿的
Who you're working with and what you're hoping
目的又是什么
to accomplish here.
你让我很不舒服
You're making me uncomfortable.
我想离开
I want to go.
抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
但是你现在应该知道 我为什么
But i'm sure you'll understand why i prefer
想现在跟你谈话了吧
To have this conversation now.
玛丽娜
Marina.
你要告诉我什么好消息啊
All right, what's this big news you got for me?
我希望是
I'm hoping it's...
不  不
No. No!
近来如何啊 典狱长
How you doing, warden?
喜欢我给你发的图片吗
You like that picture i sent you?
嘿  听到我说的话了吗
Hey! Did you hear me?!
离我女儿的东西远点
You get out of my daughter's stuff!
杰克逊
Jackson!
噢 天哪  你到底想干嘛  别挡着我  别挡路
Oh, god. What in the hell are you up to?  Out of my way. Out of my way.
喂  你敢
Hey! Don't you dare!
你给我回来 杰克逊  杰克逊
You come back here, jackson!  Jackson!
要不这样吧 让我们忘了枪这回事儿
I tell you what, how about we forget the gun?
我们痛快打一架 就像以前一样
We go hand-to-hand, just like old times.
你总是很厉害 不是吗
You always did like a good fistfight, didn't you?
当然 现在
'course, now it'd be
可能有一点不同了 不是吗
A little different, though, wouldn't it?
我要把你的每颗牙齿都打进你肚子里
I'd kick every single one of your teeth down your throat.
对 你会的 孩子
Yes, you would, son.
你是我这辈子见过的
You're the toughest son of a bitch i've ever met
最坚强的王八蛋
In my entire life.
说真的
I mean it.
第一次见到你
First time i saw you,
我就想 这孩子与众不同
I thought, "this kid is different.
这孩子很特别
This kid is special."
你  内心有着比你大一倍男孩都没有的勇气
You... Had more guts inside of you than boys twice your age.
我一直很欣赏你这一点
I always admired you for that.
闭嘴
You need to shut up.
我们曾经谈论过你 你知道
We used to talk about you, you know.
我和警卫们曾坐在一起
The guards and i used to sit back and marvel,
惊叹道  这个孩子
Saying, "this kid,
“这个吉尔·哈里斯 是一个生存者
"this gil harris, he's a survivor.
他会在另一方面变得更加强大”
He's gonna come out of this stronger on the other side."
少管所没有把你打到
Quitman didn't bring you to your knees--
它带给了你成长
It brought you to your feet.
我知道这有些难以理解
I know it's hard to understand.
我知道你很愤怒
I know that you're angry.
但我们可以坐下来 坦诚地把事情说清楚
But we can sit down man to man.
我相信我们可以解决问题
I'm sure we can work this out.
我盼这一刻已经盼了25年 雷
I've been thinking about this moment for 25 years, ray.
以牙还牙
Payback.
这是你曾对我做的每件事的报应
For everything you did to me.
你要做什么 吉尔  你要一枪打死我吗
What are you gonna do, gil? You gonna shoot me?
外面就是州长和
With the governor and...
德克萨斯一半的公路巡警
Half the texas highway patrol right outside?
我不会一枪打死你
I'm not gonna shoot you.
那太便宜你了
It's much worse than that.
我们走吧
Let's go.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
请大家注意  那TM是什么
Can i have your attention, please? What the hell is that?
我叫杰西·韦斯特  在开始之前
My name is jessie west, and i'd like to say something
我有些话想说
Before we get started.
今晚我很荣幸
Tonight i have the pleasure
能够向大家介绍真实的雷·卡罗尔
Of introducing you to the real ray carroll.
她知不知道她在做什么  让她继续说吧
What the hell does she think she's doing? Let her go.
她正说的起劲呢
She's having her moment. They say a picture is worth
人们说有图有真相 所以
A thousand words, so...
让我们以这个开头怎么样
How about we start with this?
这是一个被关在奎特曼少管所的12岁男孩
this is a 12-year-old boy who was an inmate at quitman.
在少管所里 他被雷·卡罗尔
During his time there, he was systematically drugged,
下药 虐待和折磨
Abused, and tortured by ray carroll.
让她从台上下来
Get her off the stage!
这个人利用孩子们不仅是为了牟利
This is a man who exploited children not only for profit
更是为了他自己的变态乐趣  塔特尔 把投影机关掉
But for his own sick pleasure,tuttle! Kill the projector!
是时候告诉大家真相了
And it's time to tell the truth.
雷·卡罗尔是个虐待狂
Ray carroll is a predator.
他没资格待在国会里
He doesn't belong in congress.
他应该待在监狱里
He belongs in jail.
把这个给我
Give me that.
她是
She works
我的竞争对手那边的人
For my opponent's campaign!
她在撒谎
She's lying!
我们走吧  就现在  州长先生
Let's go. Now. Governor,
整个这件事
This whole thing
都是被故意安排的
Was a setup!
她是个骗子
She's a liar!
我的未婚妻在哪儿
Where's my fianc??e?
杰克逊  告诉我她在哪儿
Jackson...You tell me where she is
要不然我一枪打爆你的头  听着
Or i put a bullet in your brain. Look,
我不知道你在说些什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
她在哪儿  你们对她做了什么
Where is she? What have you done with her?
我不知道  她在哪儿
I don't know. Where is she?!
我对上帝发誓 我真的不知道
I swear to god, i don't know.
你个婊子养的  我数三下
You son of a bitch. I'm gonna give you three
告诉我她在哪儿  否则我要你的命
And i'm taking your head off. You tell me where she is.
你想错了  告诉我她在哪儿
I'm telling you you're wrong. You tell me where she is.
我没动你的未婚妻  一
I did not touch your fianc??e. One,
二  你想错了
Two... You're wrong.
告诉我她在哪儿
Tell me where she is!
我不知道
I don't know!
杰克逊 别这么做
Jackson, don't do it.
别这么做
Don't do it!
一切都变了
Everything's changed.
他带走了玛丽娜
He's taken marina.
别这样 伙计
Come on, man.
你不是个刽子手  把枪放下
You are not a killer. Drop the gun.
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
把枪给我 伙计
Give me the gun, man.
我抓到他了
I got him.
见鬼的 怎么这么晚才来  闭嘴
The hell took you so long? Shut up.
趴下
Get on the ground!
把手放到背后
Put your hands behind your back!
你因为谋杀皮蒂·柯蒂斯而被捕
You're under arrest for the murder of petey curtis.
别让他跑了
Don't let him go.
我要把你交给警察
I will drop you.
你他妈疯了吗
You lost your damn mind?
你把我送进警局 我就杀了你弟弟
You drop me,and i kill your brother.
是吗
Yeah?
给我个理由
Give me a reason.
莉兹 别让他跑了  特里
Liz, don't let him go! Terry,
住手 莉兹 别让他跑了
Stop. Liz, don't let him go.
放倒他 莉兹
Drop him, liz.
别放他走
Don't let him go!
总要对意外情况有所准备
Always plan for the unexpected.
我得承认我没想到啊雷·卡罗尔会
I'll admit that i didn't think ray carroll would go down
以这种方式下台
Quite that way,
但我一直知道 这一天总会来的
But i always knew it was coming eventually.
并且时刻准备着
And i'm prepared.
像他那样的货色我手上多得是
I have a dozen just like him waiting in the wings.
重要的是现在特里被捕了
Important thing here is that terry's been arrested.
所以我们得按计划行事
So we have to stick to the plan.
我们要时刻保持头脑清醒
We've got to keep our heads on straight
并一路向前
And just keep moving forward.
现在你和我们也是一伙的了
With you in charge now.
我看好你 丹尼斯
I expect good things for you, dennis.
为了共同美好的未来
To a bright future together.
那杰克逊·布鲁克斯怎么办
What about jackson brooks?
我不太担心他
I wouldn't worry about him too much.
事情都在我掌控之中
I've got that situation under control.
杰克逊 我很遗憾  没关系
Jackson, i'm so sorry. That's okay.
你得到什么消息了吗  没  目前还没有
You hear anything? No? No. Nothing yet.
我向警察提交了失踪人口报告
I filed a missing persons report with the police.
他们告诉我我无能为力
They're telling me i can't do anything more,
所以 呃 我只有等着
So, uh, i got to wait.
听着 伙计  我们会找到玛丽娜的  我保证  好的
Listen, man. We're gonna find marina. I promise. That's right.
对了  你有特里的消息吗  呃 他 呃
Yeah. You hear anything about terry? Uh, he's, uh...
他还在医院
He's still in the hospital.
做手术  莉兹在等他
In surgery. Liz is waiting for him.
嘿  你有玛丽娜的消息吗
Hey. You heard anything about marina?
目前还没有  很遗憾
Nothing yet. I'm sorry.
没事
All right.
那边进行得怎么样了  嗯 我们已经查看了
What's going on here? Well, we've got
两块墓地 但我们还在找
Two graves already, but we're still looking.
干得好 肖恩  不是我 伙计
That's good work, shawnie. It wasn't me, man.
是艾米的功劳  你知道的 就是  令人伤心
All amy. You know,it's just... Really sad.
你在来这儿的路上出车祸了吗
Did you get into an accident on your way over here?
撞到了什么吗  不  不
Back into something? No. No.
不  不
No. No.
不  噢 我的天哪  噢 天哪
No! Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
不 不 不 杰克逊  杰克逊 杰克逊  不
No, no, no, jackie. Jackie, jackie... No!
不 不  找辆救护车
No, no. Get an... Get an ambulance!
救护车
Get an ambulance!
求求你了
Please.
救救她  不 不 不
Help! No, no, no.
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs80\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs87)\pos(615,555)}沉
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs80\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs87)\pos(700,555)}默
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs80\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs87)\pos(781,555)}游
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs80\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs87)\pos(861,555)}戏
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs50\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs57)\pos(406.72,261)}第
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs50\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs57)\pos(481.543,261)}一
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs50\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs57)\pos(556.366,261)}季
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs50\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs57)\pos(649.894,261)}第
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs50\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs57)\pos(727.389,261)}十
{\fade(315,2144)\fscx80\fry90\fsp5\fs50\shad0.5\bord0.3\be3\c&H9B979A&\3c&H615D60&\4c&H252124&\fn经典繁圆新\b0\t(20,1000,1\fry0\fsp7)\t(815,3560,1,\fs57)\pos(807.556,261)}集
EF字幕组译制
翻译  番茄酱 熊猫不吃竹子
翻译  捷 蓝英俊最英俊 羊蹄 小恐龙
校对 伯尼
时间轴  后菜鸟 CAP
特效  世界上最美的大宝
压制  伯尼
统筹 ZH
EF字幕组译制
关注EF字幕组新浪微博@EF字幕组
关注EF字幕组公众微信  EF字幕组
EF招新招新招新 重要的事情说三遍
招 翻译翻译翻译
招 时间轴时间轴时间轴
招 压制压制压制
EF字幕组招新群号  413712930
{\fn迷你简硬笔行书\b1\fscx0\fsp2\t(22,300,1,\fscx90)\t(1000,1100,1,\fry90)\pos(1117.76,88.011)}沉默游戏
{\fn迷你简硬笔行书\b1\fscx0\fsp2\t(22,300,1,\fscx90)\t(1000,1100,1,\fry90)\pos(1117.76,88.011)}EF字幕组
{\fn迷你简硬笔行书\b1\fscx0\fsp2\t(22,300,1,\fscx90)\move(1117.76,88.011,1117.76,128,13500,13900)\iclip(1010,80,1232,129)}沉默游戏
{\fn迷你简硬笔行书\b1\shad1\bord1\fsp2\t(22,800,1,\fscx400)\pos(1124.617,121.726)\t(13535,14578,1,\fscx0)}─
{\iclip((1010,73,1232,109))\fs41\fn迷你简硬笔行书\move(1120.286,108.429,1120.286,150.343,4779,24)}EF字幕组
{\iclip(1010,70,1232,109)\fs41\fn迷你简硬笔行书\move(1120.286,150.343,1120.286,111,5836,6253)}EF字幕组
{\fn迷你简硬笔行书\b1\fscx0\fsp2\t(22,300,1,\fscx90)\t(1000,1100,1,\fry90)\pos(1117.76,88.011)}沉默游戏
{\fn迷你简硬笔行书\b1\fscx0\fsp2\t(22,300,1,\fscx90)\t(1000,1100,1,\fry90)\pos(1117.76,88.011)}EF字幕组
{\fn迷你简硬笔行书\b1\fscx0\fsp2\t(22,300,1,\fscx90)\move(1117.76,88.011,1117.76,128,13500,13900)\iclip(1010,80,1232,129)}沉默游戏
{\fn迷你简硬笔行书\b1\fsp2\shad1\bord1\t(22,800,1,\fscx400)\pos(1124.617,121.726)\t(12535,14578,1,\fscx0)}─
{\iclip((1010,73,1232,109))\fs41\fn迷你简硬笔行书\move(1120.286,108.429,1120.286,150.343,4779,24)}EF字幕组
{\iclip(1010,70,1232,109)\fs41\fn迷你简硬笔行书\move(1120.286,150.343,1120.286,111,5543,6002)}EF字幕组
{\fn汉仪柏青体简\fs57\clip((972,46,1220,148))\t(11828,12371,1,\frx1080)\t(15000,15390,1,\fscy0)\move(1350,108,1106,108,25,900)\b1}沉默游戏
{\fn迷你简硬笔行书\b1\fsp2\shad1\bord1\t(22,800,1,\fscx500)\t(13535,14578,1,\fscx0)\pos(1112.617,143.726)}─
{\fn汉仪柏青体简\fs57\frz180\fscy0\shad0\bord0\t(25,700,1,\fscy90)\t(6000,6500,1,\frx1080\fscy0)\c&HFFFFFF&\alpha57\pos(1110,128)}戏游默沉
EF字幕组
EF字
幕组
EF字幕组
EF字
沉默游戏
EF字幕组
路
易
斯
安
那
州
欢
迎
您
地方检察官
鲍施苗圃
我在家里等你
有好消息告诉你
噢 宝贝  噢
Oh, baby. Oh...